Preliminary Guide to the Mutual Broadcasting System, Inc. records, 1952-2000 MS2083
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Source reports, undated; Series 21; 3 Linear Feet 2 cartons
  Printed materials.
  - Source reports, undated (Carton 1)
  - Source reports, undated (Carton 2)
- Miscellaneous unlabeled tapes, 1970-1989; Series 22
  Reel-to-reel audiotapes
  - Miscellaneous reels, circa 1970 - circa 1989; audiotapes (Carton 1)
  - Miscellaneous reels, circa 1970 - circa 1989; audiotapes (Carton 2)
  - Miscellaneous reels, circa 1970 - circa 1989; audiotapes (Carton 3)
  - Miscellaneous reels, circa 1970 - circa 1989; audiotapes (Carton 4)
  - Miscellaneous reels, circa 1970 - circa 1989; audiotapes (Carton 5)
  - Miscellaneous reels, circa 1970 - circa 1989; audiotapes (Carton 6)
  - Miscellaneous reels, undated; audiotapes (Carton 7)
  - Miscellaneous reels, undated; audiotapes (Carton 8)
  - Miscellaneous reels, undated; audiotapes (Carton 9)
  - Miscellaneous reels, undated; audiotapes (Carton 10)
- Phonograph collection, undated; Series 23
  - Rock USA, 1983 April 2 - 1983 June 10; Series 23 (Box 1)
  - Rock USA, 1983 June 18 - 1983 August 20; Series 23 (Box 2)
  - Rock USA, 1983 August 29 - 1983 November 12; Series 23 (Box 3)
  - Rock USA, 1983 November 19 - 1984 January 21; Series 23 (Box 4)
  - Rock USA, 1984 January 28 - 1984 February 18; Series 23 (Box 5)
  - Country Specials (1), Series 23 (Box 6)
  - Country Specials (2), Series 23 (Box 7)
  - Country Specials (3), Series 23 (Box 8)
  - National Music Survey, 1988 November 26 - 1989 April 22; Series 23 (Box 9)
  - National Music Survey, 1989 April 29 - 1989 September 9; Series 23 (Box 10)
  - National Music Survey, 1989 September 16 - 1990 January 27; Series 23 (Box 11)
  - National Music Survey, 1990 February 3 - 1990 June 30; Series 23 (Box 12)
  - Live from Gilley's, 1986 March 3 - 1986 August 3; Series 23 (Box 13)
  - Adult Contemporary Comments, 1985 August 5 - 1986 March 31; Series 23 (Box 14)
  - Adult Contemporary Comments, 1986 April 7 - 1986 September 24; Series 23 (Box 15)
  - Adult Contemporary Comments, 1986 December 1 - 1987 March 23; Series 23 (Box 16)
  - Unordered Master Tapes (1), Series 23 (Box 17)
  - Unordered Master Tapes (2), Series 23 (Box 18)
  - Unordered Master Tapes (3), Series 23 (Box 19)
  - Unordered Master Tapes (4), Series 23 (Box 20)
  - Unordered Master Tapes (5), Series 23 (Box 21)
  - Unordered Master Tapes (6), Series 23 (Box 22)
  - Unordered Master Tapes (7), Series 23 (Box 23)
  - Unordered Master Tapes (8), Series 23 (Box 24)
  - Unordered Master Tapes (9), Series 23 (Box 25)
  - Unordered Master Tapes (10), Series 23 (Box 26)
  - Assorted Records, Series 23 (Box 27)
  - Assorted Albums, Series 23 (Box 28)
  - Assorted Albums, Series 23 (Box 29)
  - Dick Clark's National Music Survey, 1985 January 12 - 1985 June 1; Series 23 (Box 30)
  - Dick Clark's National Music Survey, 1985 June 8 - 1985 October 19; Series 23 (Box 31)
  - Dick Clark's National Music Survey, 1985 October 26 - 1986 March 22; Series 23 (Box 32)
  - Dick Clark's National Music Survey, 1986 March 29 - 1986 July 19; Series 23 (Box 33)
  - Assorted Records, Series 23 (Box 34)
  - Unmarked, Series 23 (Box 35)
  - Unmarked, Series 23 (Box 36)
  - Unmarked, Series 23 (Box 37)
  - Unmarked, Series 23 (Box 38)
  - Dick Clark's National Music Survey, 1985 January 19 - 1985 March 16; Series 23 (Box 39)
  - Dick Clark's National Music Survey, 1985 March 23 - 1985 June 6; Series 23 (Box 40)
  - Dick Clark's National Music Survey, 1985 July 13 - 1985 October 26; Series 23 (Box 41)
  - Dick Clark's National Music Survey, 1985 November 2 - 1986 March 16; Series 23 (Box 42)
  - Unsorted Albums, Series 23 (Box 43)
  - Unsorted Albums, Series 23 (Box 44)
  - Unsorted Albums, Series 23 (Box 45)
  - Unsorted Albums, Series 23 (Box 46)
  - Unsorted Albums, Series 23 (Box 47)
  - Dick Clark's National Music Survey, 1983 July 16 - 1983 September 24; Series 23 (Box 48)
  - Dick Clark's National Music Survey, 1983 October 1 - 1983 November 26; Series 23 (Box 49)
  - Dick Clark's National Music Survey, 1983 December 3 - 1984 Frebruary 4; Series 23 (Box 50)
  - Dick Clark's National Music Survey and Assorted Albums, 1984 February 18 - 1984 March 3; Series 23 (Box 51)
  - Dick Clark's National Music Survey, 1984 April 14 - 1984 July 28; Series 23 (Box 52)
  - Dick Clark's National Music Survey, 1984 August 4 - 1984 October 13; Series 23 (Box 53)
  - Dick Clark's National Music Survey, 1984 October 20 - 1984 December 15; Series 23 (Box 54)
  - Dick Clark's National Music Survey, 1984 December 22 - 1985 January 5; Series 23 (Box 55)
  - On a Country Road, 1989 September 2 - 1990 January 13; Series 23 (Box 56)
  - On a Country Road, 1990 January 20 - 1990 June 2; Series 23 (Box 57)
  - On a Country Road, 1990 June 9 - 1990 November 3; Series 23 (Box 58)
  - On a Country Road, 1990 November 10 - 1991 March 16; Series 23 (Box 59)
  - National Music Survey, 1986 July 26 - 1986 December 13; Series 23 (Box 60)
  - National Music Survey, 1986 December 20 - 1987 May 2; Series 23 (Box 61)
  - National Music Survey, 1987 May 9 - 1987 October 3; Series 23 (Box 62)
  - National Music Survey, 1987 October 10 - 1988 February 20; Series 23 (Box 63)
  - Unsorted Albums, Series 23 (Box 64)
  - Unsorted Albums, Series 23 (Box 65)
  - Unsorted Albums, Series 23 (Box 66)
  - Unsorted Albums, Series 23 (Box 67)
  - Unsorted Albums, Series 23 (Box 68)
  - Unsorted Albums, Series 23 (Box 69)
  - Unsorted Albums, Series 23 (Box 70)
  - Unsorted Albums, Series 23 (Box 71)
  - Unsorted Albums, Series 23 (Box 72)
  - Unsorted Albums, Series 23 (Box 73)
  - Country Specials, Series 23 (Box 74)
  - Country Specials, Series 23 (Box 75)
  - Country Specials, Series 23 (Box 76)
  - On a Country Road, 1988 February 6 - 1988 July 2; Series 23 (Box 77)
  - On a Country Road, Series 23 (Box 78)
  - On a Country Road, 1988 December 10 - 1989 April 22; Series 23 (Box 79)
  - On a Country Road, 1989 April 29 - 1989 September 9; Series 23 (Box 80)
  - Competitors' Programs, Series 23 (Box 81)
  - Competitors' Programs, Series 23 (Box 82)
  - Competitors' Programs, Series 23 (Box 83)
  - Competitors' Programs, Series 23 (Box 84)
  - Competitors' Programs, Series 23 (Box 85)
  - Mutual Radio Theater Master Tapes, Series 23 (Box 86)
  - Mutual Radio Theater Master Tapes, Series 23 (Box 87)
  - Mutual Radio Theater Master Tapes, Series 23 (Box 88)
  - Mutual Radio Theater Master Tapes, Series 23 (Box 89)
  - Mutual Radio Theater, 1980 March 3 - 1980 April 28; Series 23 (Box 90)
  - Mutual Radio Theater, 1980 May 5 - 1980 June 23; Series 23 (Box 91)
  - Mutual Radio Theater, 1980 July 14; Series 23 (Box 92)
  - Mutual Radio Theater, 1980 September 9 - 1980 December 15; Series 23 (Box 93)
  - Mutual Radio Theater, 1980 September 16 - 1980 September 22; Series 23 (Box 94)
  - Country Specials, Series 23 (Box 95)
  - Country Specials, Series 23 (Box 96)
  - National Lampoon's True Facts, 1985 March 4 - 1985 December 2; Series 23 (Box 97)
  - Listen In With, 1989 December 2 - 1990 June 6; Series 23 (Box 98)
  - Listen In With, 1989 February 5 - 1989 November 25; Series 23 (Box 99)
  - Country Music Specials, Series 23 (Box 101)
  - Country Music Specials, Series 23 (Box 102)
  - Country Music Specials, Series 23 (Box 103)
  - Adult Contemporary Specials, Series 23 (Box 104)
  - Adult Contemporary Specials, Series 23 (Box 105)
  - Adult Contemporary Specials, Series 23 (Box 106)
  - Adult Contemporary Specials, Series 23 (Box 107)
  - Adult Contemporary Specials, Series 23 (Box 108)
  - Adult Contemporary Specials, Series 23 (Box 109)
  - Adult Contemporary Specials, Series 23 (Box 110)
  - Adult Contemporary Specials, Series 23 (Box 111)
  - 12" Vinyls, Series 23 (Box 112)
  - 12" Vinyls, Series 23 (Box 113)
  - 12" Vinyls, Series 23 (Box 114)
  - 12" Vinyls, Series 23 (Box 115)
  - 12" Vinyls, Series 23 (Box 116)
  - National Lampoon's True Facts, Series 23 (Box 117)
  - National Lampoon's True Facts, Series 23 (Box 118)
  - National Lampoon's True Facts, Series 23 (Box 119)
  - National Lampoon's True Facts, Series 23 (Box 120)
  - National Lampoon's True Facts, Series 23 (Box 121)
  - National Lampoon's True Facts, Series 23 (Box 122)
  - National Music Survey, 1982 October 30 - 1983 January 1; Series 23 (Box 123)
  - National Music Survey, 1983 January 8 - 1983 March 3; Series 23 (Box 124)
  - National Music Survey, 1983 March 12 - 1983 May 7; Series 23 (Box 125)
  - National Music Survey, 1983 May 14 - 1983 July 9; Series 23 (Box 126)
  - On a Country Road, 1991 March 22 - 1991 July 20; Series 23 (Box 127)
  - On a Country Road, 1991 July 27 - 1991 December 14; Series 23 (Box 128)
  - On a Country Road, 1991 December 22 - 1992 March 28; Series 23 (Box 129)
  - Adult Contemporary Specials, Series 23 (Box 130)
  - Adult Contemporary Specials, Series 23 (Box 131)
  - Adult Contemporary Specials, Series 23 (Box 132)
  - Adult Contemporary Specials, Series 23 (Box 133)
  - Adult Contemporary Specials, Series 23 (Box 134)
  - Country Specials, Series 23 (Box 135)
  - Country Specials, Series 23 (Box 136)
  - Country Specials, Series 23 (Box 137)
  - LACR, 1984 August 11 - 1984 October 20; Series 23 (Box 138)
  - LACR, 1984 October 13 - 1984 December 15; Series 23 (Box 139)
  - LACR, 1984 December 22 - 1985 April 13; Series 23 (Box 140)
  - LACR, 1985 April 20 - 1985 July 27; Series 23 (Box 141)
  - 12" Vinyl, Series 23 (Binder 142)
  - 12" Vinyl, Series 23 (Box 143)
  - 12" Vinyl, Series 23 (Box 144)
  - 12" Vinyl, Series 23 (Box 145)
  - 12" Vinyl, Series 23 (Box 146)
  - National Music Survey, 1988 January 11 - 1988 July 9; Series 23 (Box 147)
  - National Music Survey, 1988 July 16 - 1988 November 19; Series 23 (Box 148)
  - National Music Survey, 1981 May 30 - 1981 June 18; Series 23 (Box 149)
  - National Music Survey, 1981 July 25 - 1981 September 12; Series 23 (Box 150)
  - National Music Survey, 1981 September 19 - 1981 November 21; Series 23 (Box 151)
  - National Music Survey, 1981 November 28 - 1982 January 23; Series 23 (Box 152)
  - National Music Survey, 1982 January 30 - 1982 March 27; Series 23 (Box 153)
  - National Music Survey, 1982 April 3 - 1982 May 29; Series 23 (Box 154)
  - National Music Survey, 1982 June 5 - 1982 July 31; Series 23 (Box 155)
  - National Music Survey, 1982 August 7 - 1982 September 25; Series 23 (Box 156A)
  - National Music Survey, 1982 October 3 - 1982 October 23; Series 23 (Box 156B)
  - 12" Vinyl, Series 23 (Box 157)
  - 12" Vinyl, Series 23 (Box 158)
  - 12" Vinyl, Series 23 (Box 159)
  - 12" Vinyl, Series 23 (Box 160)
  - 12" Vinyl, Series 23 (Box 161)
  - Mutual Radio Theater Master Tape, Series 23 (Box 162)
  - Mutual Radio Theater Master Tape, Series 23 (Box 163)
  - Mutual Radio Theater Master Tape, Series 23 (Box 164)
  - Mutual Radio Theater Master Tape, Series 23 (Box 165)
  - Mutual Radio Theater Master Tape, Series 23 (Box 166)
  - 12" Vinyl, Series 23 (Box 167)
  - 12" Vinyl, Series 23 (Box 168)
  - 12" Vinyl, Series 23 (Box 169)
  - 12" Vinyl, Series 23 (Box 170)
  - LACR, 1983 October 29 - 1983 December 31; Series 23 (Box 171)
  - LACR, 1984 January 7 - 1984 March 10; Series 23 (Box 172)
  - LACR, 1984 March 17 - 1984 May 9; Series 23 (Box 173)
  - LACR, 1984 May 26 - 1984 August 4; Series 23 (Box 174)
  - Country Comments, 1985 August - 1986 March 31; Series 23 (Box 175)
  - Country Comments, 1986 April 7 - 1986 November 10; Series 23 (Box 176)
  - Country Comments, 1986 November 17 - 1987 May 4; Series 23 (Box 177)
  - Country Comments, 1987 May 11 - 1987 October 5; Series 23 (Box 178)
  - Country Comments, Series 23 (Box 179)
  - Country Comments, Series 23 (Box 180)
  - Country Comments, Series 23 (Box 181)
  - Country Comments, Series 23 (Box 182)
  - 12" Vinyl Masters, Series 23 (Box 183)
  - 12" Vinyl Masters, Series 23 (Box 184)
  - 12" Vinyl Masters, Series 23 (Box 185)
  - LACR, 1983 January 15 - 1983 March 12; Series 23 (Box 186)
  - LACR, 1983 March 12 - 1983 May 14; Series 23 (Box 187)
  - LACR, 1983 May 21 - 1983 July 23; Series 23 (Box 188)
  - LACR, 1983 July 30 - 1983 October 1; Series 23 (Box 189)
  - LACR, 1985 August 3 - 1985 November 23; Series 23 (Box 190)
  - LACR, 1985 November 30 - 1986 April 12; Series 23 (Box 191)
  - LACR, 1986 April 8 - 1986 September 6; Series 23 (Box 192)
  - LACR, 1986 September 13 - 1987 January 24; Series 23 (Box 193)
  - LACR, 1987 January 24 - 1987 April 4; Series 23 (Box 194)
  - LACR, 1987 April 11 - 1987 June 20; Series 23 (Box 195)
  - LACR, 1987 June 27 - 1987 September 19; Series 23 (Box 196)
  - LACR, 1987 September 26 - 1988 January 30; Series 23 (Box 197)
  - National Music Survey, 1984 April 7 - 1984 June 9; Series 23 (Box 198)
  - National Music Survey, 1984 June 30 - 1984 September 15; Series 23 (Box 199)
  - National Music Survey, 1984 September 22 - 1984 November 10; Series 23 (Box 200)
  - National Music Survey, 1984 November 17 - 1985 January 12; Series 23 (Box 201)
  - Live from Gilley's, Series 23 (Box 202)
  - Live from Gilley's, Series 23 (Box 203)
  - Live from Gilley's, Series 23 (Box 204)
  - Live from Gilley's, Series 23 (Box 205)
- Mutual News recordings, Series 24
  Arranged in no particular order
  - Tammy Wynette, 1992 May 12; Series 24 (Box 1, Reel 1)
  - Tammy Wynette Country music awards, 1991; Series 24 (Box 1, Reel 2)
  - Tammy Wynette, Undated; Series 24 (Box 1, Reel 3)
  - Lowell Thomas, Undated; Series 24 (Box 1, Reel 4)
  - Ginger Rogers, 1991 October 9; Series 24 (Box 1, Reel 5)
    Obit file Ginger Rogers interview Today Show 1991 October 9 Interviewed by Katie Couric 8:50 am
  - HFR Dang Xiao Ping Death, 1989 September 13; Series 24 (Box 2, Reel 1)
  - Claude Colbert, Undated; Series 24 (Box 2, Reel 2)
  - Art Carney, 1991 November 19; Series 24 (Box 2, Reel 3)
  - Art Carney obit Today show interview, 1981 December 1; Series 24 (Box 2, Reel 4)
  - Art Carney phone interview, 1996 February 04; Series 24 (Box 2, Reel 5)
  - George Burns Ack Feed, Undated; Series 24 (Box 3, Reel 1)
  - George Burns Appreication, Undated; Series 24 (Box 3, Reel 2)
  - Cardinal Bernadin, Undated; Series 24 (Box 3, Reel 3)
  - Cardinal Bernadin, September 08; Series 24 (Box 3, Reel 4)
  - Red Barber, 1985 August 26; Series 24 (Box 3, Reel 5)
  - Wayne Alwyne and Russi Taylor, July 10; Series 24 (Box 3, Reel 6)
  - James Michner Intro, 1992 February 05; Series 24 (Box 4, Reel 1)
  - Jim Bohannon interview with James Michner, 1990 May 11; Series 24 (Box 4, Reel 2)
  - Michner LKS dub, 1989 December 07; Series 24 (Box 4, Reel 3)
  - Mastriani obit, Undated; Series 24 (Box 4, Reel 4)
  - Joseph L. Mankiewitz, 1986; Series 24 (Box 4, Reel 5)
- Network tape files (NBC), Circa 1945 - 1987; Series 25; 7 Linear Feet 28 card file boxes
  Arranged chronologically
  This series consists of index cards with topics and information about programs. All these original card files had a note that read "tapes are at NBC studios."
  - Pre-1965 A -, Circa 1945-1964; Series 25 (Box 1)
  - pre-1965 B-D, Circa 1945-1964; Series 25 (Box 2)
  - Pre-1965 D-H, Circa 1945-1964; Series 25 (Box 3)
  - Pre-1965 H-Mc, Circa 1945-1964; Series 25 (Box 4)
  - Pre-1965 Mc-R, Circa 1945-1964; Series 25 (Box 5)
  - Pre-1965 R-T, Circa 1945-1964; Series 25 (Box 6)
  - Pre-1965 U-Z, Circa 1945-1964; Series 25 (Box 7)
  - A-D, 1965-1974; Series 25 (Box 8)
  - E-J, 1965-1974; Series 25 (Box 9)
  - K-M, 1965-1974; Series 25 (Box 10)
  - O-S, 1965-1974; Series 25 (Box 11)
  - T-Z, 1965-1974; Series 25 (Box 12)
  - A-C, 1975-1976; Series 25 (Box 12)
  - C-H, 1975-1976; Series 25 (Box 13)
  - I-O, 1975-1976; Series 25 (Box 14)
  - P-Z, 1975-1976; Series 25 (Box 15)
  - A-D, 1977-1978; Series 25 (Box 16)
  - E-L, 1977-1978; Series 25 (Box 17)
  - M-S, 1977-1978; Series 25 (Box 18)
  - T-Z, 1977-1978; Series 25 (Box 19)
  - A-D, 1979-1981; Series 25 (Box 19)
  - E-O, 1979-1981; Series 25 (Box 20)
  - P-Z, 1979-1981; Series 25 (Box 21)
  - A-C, 1982; Series 25 (Box 21)
  - D-R, 1982; Series 25 (Box 22)
  - S-Z, 1982; Series 25 (Box 23)
  - A-F, 1983; Series 25 (Box 23)
  - G-R, 1983; Series 25 (Box 24)
  - S-Z, 1983; Series 25 (Box 25)
  - A-G, 1984; Series 25 (Box 25)
  - H-Z, 1984; Series 25 (Box 26)
  - A-C, 1985; Series 25 (Box 26)
  - D-Z, 1985; Series 25 (Box 27)
  - A-Z, 1986; Series 25 (Box 28)
  - A-C, 1987; Series 25 (Box 28)
  - D-Z, 1987; Series 25 (Box 1)